-怎么了   -地铁上有人舔我的脖子
- What's the matter? - Somebody on the subway licked my neck!
威利还活着
Willy's still alive!
-你们在做什么   -我妈打过电话
- What are you guys doing? - My mom called.
他们要登报通知亲友  我们订婚了
They're announcing our engagement in the paper.
我们要找一张很漂亮的合照
We're looking for a good picture of us.
恐怕我们就没有好看的合照
I'm afraid that does not exist.
我们合拍了很多不错的照片
There are great pictures of us.
不  你照的很好
No, there are great pictures of you
但你旁边的男人是这样的
standing next to a guy who's going like this.
天啊  他就是
Oh, my God, That's the creep
在自由女神像旁跟你合照的怪胎
that you're with at the Statue of Liberty.
我不知道为什么 我就是不会照相
I don't know what it is. I just can't take a good picture.
这一张很不错
Here's a great one.
-那一张没有我  -是  但我全身晒得黑亮
- Yeah, I'm not in that. - No, but look at me, all tan.
你们为什么不请
Why don't you go get portraits done
专业摄影师帮你们拍照呢
by a professional photographer?
那是个好点子  他们一定有大风扇
That's a great idea. I bet they have one of those wind machines.
那很棒
Yeah, that's great.
你真的那么做的话钱德勒应该看起来没那么蠢
Next to that, Chandler won't look so stupid.
钱德勒你觉得呢   -没问题  但我要警告你
Chandler, what do you say? - All right, I should warn you.
去的不是我  是这个"我"
But I'm not going. "I'm" Going.
兄弟  那一记反手投篮帅呆了
Dude, that reverse lay-up.
-那三分球呢   -出神入化
- And how about those three-pointers? - Amazing.
这次也是差一点那些家伙就答应让我们上场了
And those guys were this close to letting us play this time too.
你们看  菲比在跟咖啡厅帅哥说话
Hey, look. Phoebe's talking to Cute Coffeehouse Guy.
你叫他"咖啡厅帅哥"吗
You call him, "Cute Coffeehouse Guy"?
我们叫他"边尿边哼歌先生"
We call him, "Hums While He Pees."
我们管罗斯叫"浴室磨蹭鬼"
Yes, and we call Ross, "Lingers in the Bathroom."
"边尿边哼歌先生"刚刚约我出去
Hey, you guys, Hums While He Pees just asked me out!
我以为他结婚了
I thought that guy was married.
对  但他正在办离婚
He is, but he's getting divorced.
罗斯  或许你认识他
Ross, maybe you know him.
又不是俱乐部
It's not a club.
如果他正在办离婚 你觉得跟他约会合适吗
If he's getting a divorce, is it such a good idea to date him?
离婚男人不是坏男人
Hey, divorced men are not bad men.
他们把那句话印在俱乐部的纸巾
They have that on the napkins at the club.
我得回去上班了
I gotta get back to work.
你还可以休息半小时
You don't have to be back for a half-hour.
我的助理泰格午餐时会在办公室做仰卧起坐
My assistant, Tag, does sit-ups in the office during lunch.
他就像黄油果酱一样香甜可口
I could just spread him on a cracker.
你在暗恋他  为什么还要雇用他
You have a crush on him, why would you hire him?
你知道你不能跟他约会对吧
You know you can't date him, right?
对  我知道
Oh, no, I know that.
我们开玩笑说  因为我们太常在一起
We made a joke that we spend so much time together...
他应该叫我"工作上的太大"
...he should call me, his "Work-wife."
很快的他就可以叫你
Soon he'll be able to call you,
"那个被开除的女人"
"That lady he knew that got fired."
我不会被开除  因为我不会采取行动
I'm not gonna get fired, because I'm not gonna act on it.
你不会介意他跟别人约会吧
You wouldn't mind if he was dating someone else?
怎么了  他有吗  他有
Why, is he? He is, isn't he?
他在跟市场部那个荡妇约会
He's dating that slut in marketing.
或许我该成立一个离婚男子俱乐部
Maybe I should open a divorced men's club.
兄弟  那太惨了
Dude, that's so sad.
我会在后院设一个篮球场
I could put a basketball court in the back.
我能一起打球吗
Could I play?
今天不做仰卧起坐吗   泰格
Oh, no sit-ups today, Tag?
-我刚刚做完  -再做十下吧
- I just did them. - Well, drop and give me 10 more.
什么
What?
我午餐喝了酒
I had a drink with lunch.
成本报告送过来了吗
Did those cost reports come in?
送来了  我昨晚就已经归档了
Yes, I filled them out last night.
麻烦你帮我影印四份
Could you make me four copies?
-没问题  -太棒了  谢谢你
- Sure. - Great, thank you.
-瑞秋  -梅丽莎 有什么事吗
- Hey, Rachel. - Hi, Melissa. What's up?
我正好要去买东西
I'm just about to go out to the store.
买些东西放进我的背包里
Get some stuff to put in my backpack.
水果干  速食麦片  那一类的东西
Dried fruit, and granola and stuff like that.
-有什么事吗   -泰格在吗
- What's up? - Is Tag here?
他不在  怎么了
No. Why?
我来问他  今晚要做什么
I was gonna talk to him about doing something  tonight.
真的吗   你喜欢泰格  对吧
Really? You got a little crush on Tag there, do you?
我们一直都在眉来眼去的
We've been flirting back and forth...
但我希望今晚
...but I was hoping tonight
事情能有点进展
it would turn into something a little more than that.
别猴急  梅丽莎  这里不是更衣室
Easy there, Melissa. This ain't a locker room, okay.
但我记得他说过  今晚他已经有约了
But, you know, I remember him saying that he had plans tonight.
-不是吧  -是
- Oh, no. - Oh, yeah.
好吧  快回去工作
All right, back to work.
那不是泰格的背包吗
Hey, isn't that Tag's backpack?
我不想落下办公室贱人的名称
I don't want to be known as the office bitch,
但是我会给你的领导打电话
but I'll call your supervisor.
太棒了  非常不错  莫妮卡
Great, that's great, Monica. Great.
好了  钱德勒  你能笑一个吗
Now, Chandler, you want to give us a smile?
好
Okay.
抱歉  那张椅子很不舒服吗
I'm sorry, is the seat uncomfortable?
不  是我很不舒服
No, I am.
钱德勒  我知道你办得到  你笑起来很帅
Chandler, I know you can do this. You have a beautiful smile.
-是吗  -对
- I do? - Yeah.
或许你不必笑  我们来试试别的点子
Maybe you don't have to smile.Let's try something else.
-试着性感  -好吧
- Try looking sexy. - Okay.
别试了也好
Or not.
乔伊  你在这里做什么
Hi, Joey, what are you doing here?
我要在这条街上试镜
I got an audition down the street,
结果酱汁沾到衣服上了
and I spilled sauce on my shirt.
-有多余衬衫吗  -当然
- You got an extra one? - Yeah, sure.
拿去
Here.
太棒了
Great.
有除了拉夫罗兰外其他品牌吗
You got anything that's not Ralph Lauren?
应该没有  乔伊
Yeah, I don't think so, Joe.
我猜这件应该可以
I guess this'll be fine.
-你今晚要做什么   -没事  怎么了
- What are you doing tonight? - Nothing. Why?
带我的助理泰格出去玩吧   我付钱
How would you feel about taking out my assistant, Tag? I'll pay.
要我跟男人出去约会
It's gonna take a lot of money for me
可得付我一大笔钱
to go out on a date with a dude.
我不是要你跟他约会
I'm not asking you to go on a date with him.
真的吗   因为我真的很缺钱
Really? Because I could kind of use the money.
他刚搬到这里  我知道他没有男性朋友
He's new in town, and I know he doesn't have any guy friends.
带他去看球赛或做别的事  谢谢了
Take him to a ball game or something.I'd really appreciate it.
-好的  没问题  -谢谢你
- Yeah, okay, no problem. - Thank you.
是甜甜圈
Ooh, hey, doughnuts!
我知道  我们来试试看
I know. Let's try a look...
凝视我们的未来
...of far-off wonderment.
想想我们的婚姻
Gaze into our future,
跟我们未来的日子
and think about our marriage and the days to come.
钱德勒  你的脸到底是怎么了
Chandler, what is the matter with your face?
这张照片应该要表达"盖勒和宾要结婚了"
This picture should say, "Geller and Bing to be married,"...
而非"英勇女市民勇救溺水弱智"
...not, "Local woman saves drowning moron."
别笑他  他是我的溺水弱智
Hey, don't laugh at him. He's my drowning moron.
对了  就是这样  快拍下来
That's it, that's it! Take it, take it!
我喜欢这一张
I like this one.
好像是在说"我爱你  所以我要杀了你"
It seems to say, "I love you and that's why I have to kill you."
不可能每一张都那么糟啊
Can't all be bad.
找那张你装出睡眼惺忪的照片
Find the one where you make your bedroom eyes.
这张
There it is.
这是我睡眼惺忪的样子
Oh, my God, those are my bedroom eyes?
你为什么要跟我同床共枕
Why did you ever sleep with me?
你真的想提这件事情吗
Do you really want to pull at that thread?
-我真的玩得很开心  -我也是
- I'm really having a good time. - Me too.
地铁里那人舔了你的脖子真是让人觉得抱歉
Sorry that guy on the subway licked your neck.
不  没关系  他是我们的朋友
No, that's okay. He's a friend.
恕我唐突
I don't mean to be presumptuous...
但我有明天国标舞总决赛的门票
...but I have tickets to the ballroom-dancing finals tomorrow.
就  我
Yeah, I...
我没看半决赛  所以看决赛可能由点迷茫
Well, I missed the semifinals, so I think I would just be lost.
我知道那真的很无聊
I know that it's really lame,
但这些票是我的老板给我...
but I got these tickets from my boss...
不  我的天啊
Oh, no, no, no, my God!
好了  别大惊小怪  我去就是
Okay, don't freak out. I'll go.
是我的前妻惠特妮
It's my ex-wife, Whitney.
我现在没办法面对她  那个女人疯了
I cannot deal with her now. That woman is crazy.
好吧  我知道  等一下
Okay, I know. Hold on.
-罗斯  -什么事
- Hey, Ross. - Yeah.
凯尔的前妻惠特妮就在外面
That's Whitney, Kyle's ex-wife, out there.
你可以把她诱开让我们脱身吗
Do you think you could divert her so we could slip out?
什么   不
What? No.
好吧  但我有两张国标舞总决赛的门票
Okay, but I have two tickets to the ballroom-dance finals.
还是算了  菲比
I don't think so, Pheebs.
好吧  我愿意
All right, I'll do it.
-但那只是因为你是我的朋友  -好吧
- But just because you're a friend. - Okay.
嗨  舞王
Hi, Ginger.
我要拿回我的钥匙
I want my key back.
-我没有  -就在你收上
- I don't have it. - It's right there.
行吧  福尔摩斯
Okay, Sherlock.
对不起  但你最好快点离开  菲比
I'm sorry, but you'd better go, Pheebs.
我只是要谢谢你帮我们诱开凯尔的前妻
I just wanted to thank you, though, for diverting Kyle's ex.
别客气  待会再谈
You're welcome. We'll talk about it later.
-嗨  惠特妮  -嗨  罗斯
- Hi, Whitney. - Hi, Ross.
-去吃早餐吧  -好
- Are you ready for breakfast? - Yep.
凯尔的前妻    你应该要诱开她不是跟她约会
Kyle's ex-wife? You were supposed to divert her, not date her.
你能不能等我一下   我得跟这个女人谈一谈
Can you give me a second while I talk to this woman...
而且  她没有在这里过夜
...who, by the way, did not spend the night?
-没问题  -好吧
- Sure. - Okay.
我的确诱开她了 后来我们玩得很开心
I did divert her, and we ended up having a great time, okay?
你们一起去看国标舞了
Watching ballroom dancing?
对  那时我们发现我们都很酷
Yes, that's where we realized we were both super-cool people.
听着  凯尔告诉我她有些缺点
Look, Kyle just told me some really bad stuff about her.
-譬如说呢   -譬如说她很无情
- Like what? - Like she's really mean...
她吹毛求疵
...and she's overly critical and...
她会不经过你的同意
She will paint a room a really
把房间漆成很明亮的颜色
bright color without even checking with you.
好吧
Okay.
她还会把性当成武器
And she uses sex as a weapon.
谢谢你的警告
Thank you for warning me.
吃早餐时我会注意油漆跟性武器
At breakfast, I'll be on alert for room painting and sex weapons.
-你还是要跟她约会   -对
- You're still gonna go out with her? - Yeah.
你没有听到刚刚我说的话吗
Well, didn't you hear what I just said?
菲比  少来了  你的消息来源有问题
Pheebs, come on. I mean, consider the source.
她的前夫当然会那么说
Of course her ex-husband's gonna say that.
现在  请你离开
Now, if you'll excuse me.
听我说  她疯了
Listen to me, she is crazy!
你的门没有隔音功能
Your door isn't soundproof.
看到了吧   她就是爱挑剔
You see? Nothing is good enough for her.
-早安  -嗨  泰格
- Morning. - Hi, Tag.
昨晚你跟乔伊玩得开心吗
Did you have fun with Joey last night?
我们去看纽约队比赛了
Yeah, we went to the Knicks game.
那真的太棒了
That's nice.
然后我们去酒吧玩  他帮我们泡上好多女人
Then we went to a bar, and he hooked us up with all these women.
女人   你是说老女人
Women? You mean, like old women?
还好吧  30岁左右
Kind of old, like 30.
我以前没办法在酒吧里跟女人聊天
I never used to be able to just talk to girls in bars...
但昨晚我就拿到了二十个电话号码
...but I got like 20 phone numbers last night.
那真的是太棒了
That's great.
乔伊真的教会你一些事
Joey must have really taught you some stuff.
一点吧
A little.
你好吗
How you doing?
看吧那个笑容非常灿烂  放轻松  自然
See? That's a great smile. Easy, natural.
现在假装我手上拿了照相机
Now pretend I have a camera.
-你又变了  -我控制不了
- You're changing it. - I can't help it.
你想知道  我都是怎么简历照片的吗
You want to know what I do when I take resume shots?
跟我借钱拍
Borrow money from me?
对  好吧  首先你得装出自然的样子
Yeah. Okay, first of all, you want to make it look spontaneous.
我都是这么做的 我会低头  继续低头
So here's what I do. I look down, look down, keep looking down.
然后抬头
Then I look up.
看到没   现在你来试试看
See? Now you try.
低头  低头  继续低头
Look down. You're looking down. Keep looking down.
你的鞋子上为什么会有果酱
Why is there jelly on your shoe?
我吃甜甜圈了
I had a doughnut.
听说昨晚你跟泰格玩得很开心
So I heard you had some fun with Tag last night.
对  那家伙还不错
Yeah, that guy's all right.
对  教出另一个"乔伊"你很开心吧
Yeah, and you had fun teaching him how to be all "Joey."
-什么   -你懂的  泡妞
- What? - You know, all the women.
泡妞技巧是学不来的
You can't teach someone to be good with women.
所以我跟钱德勒出去老是泡不到妞
That's why I never had any luck with Chandler.
我就在这里
I'm right here.
你能不能别再跟他一起出去
Would you mind just not going out with him again?
就是你跟他一起去泡妞
Just the idea of you, and he, and all these women...
我知道他是我的助理  我不能跟他约会
I know he's my assistant, and I can't date him!
但这真的让我很困扰  好吗
But it just bothers me, all right?
你不能抢走他
No, no, no, you can't take him away from me.
我好不容易找了个泡妞搭档
I got a great partner to pick up girls with. Finally!
我还在这里
I'm still right here.
至少你可以跟他谈一谈
Will you at least talk to him...
告诉他跟一大堆女人约会既空虚
...and tell him how hollow and
又得不到满足
unsatisfying this dating-tons-of-women thing is?
什么
What?
在我不喜欢他之前  我不要他跟任何人约会
I just don't want him to meet anybody until I'm over my crush.
我会忘记他的
And I will get over it.
我并不爱他  那只是肉体上的吸引力
It's not like I love him. It's just physical.
我常常这样暗恋男人
I get crushes like this all the time.
刚认识你时我就暗恋过你
I had a crush on you at first.
我知道  莫妮卡跟我说过
I know. Monica told me.
我们刚认识时你暗恋过我吗
Did you have a crush on me when we first met?
对  有啊
Yeah, sure.
难道你们就是看不到我吗
Can you people not see me?
你能跟他谈谈吗
Will you talk to him?
我不知道  瑞秋
I don't know, Rach.
我会送你十件拉夫罗兰的衬衫
I'll give you 10 free Ralph Lauren shirts.
一件
One.
不  十件  你说十件  你不能反梅
No, 10. You said 10. You can't take that back.
你有事要跟我谈
You wanted to talk to me?
我不知道  你拿了东西来给我吗
I don't know. You got something for me?
对  这是瑞秋要给你的
Yeah, this is from Rachel.
十件  好吧
Ten. Okay.
泰格  跟太多女人约会是不好的
Tag, there's such a thing as too many women.
-真的吗  - 对你来说是的
- Really? - Yeah, for you.
-嘿  你来了  -我来了
- Hey, there you are- There I am.
-你没事吧   -没事  乔伊说我要放松
- You okay? - Yeah, Joey said I needed to relax.
他给我吃了抗组胺药
So he gave me an antihistamine.
什么
What?
我搭地铁时睡着了结果到了布鲁克林
I fell asleep on the subway and went to Brooklyn.
布鲁克林好远
Brooklyn is far.
你在想什么
What were you thinking?
别担心   因为现在我知道要怎么拍照了
But don't worry, because I know how to take a picture now.
好了  看吧  低头
Okay, see. Look down.
低头
Look down.
-钱德勒  -怎么了
- Chandler? - Yeah?
-嗨  -嗨
- Hi. - Hi.
你跟疯婆子还好吧
How are things going with Crazy?
她把你的兔子拿去煮了吗
Has she cooked your rabbit yet?
你听到的只是片面之词  好吗
Listen, you are hearing one side of the story. Okay?
还有  她拿了二十份油漆样本给凯尔看
FYI, she must have shown Kyle over 30 paint samples...
之后她才动手漆房间
...before she painted that room.
他对每一份样本的反应都是
And his response to each one was,
"我一点都不在乎"
"I don't give a tiny rat's ass."
或许她该少花点时间在装潢上
Maybe she should have spent a little less time decorating...
多花一点时间在卧室里
...and a little more time in the bedroom.
我想我们不会有那样的问题
I don't think we are going to have that problem...
但或许那是因为
...but maybe that's just
我不会吝于付出感情
because I am not emotionally unavailable.
你认为他吝于付出感情
You think he's emotionally unavailable?
我想有那个可能
I think he can be.
如果她没有
Maybe he wouldn't be...
每晚把公事带因家做或许他就不会那样子
...if she didn't bring the office home every night.
你得原谅她知道该怎么面对她的生活
Excuse her for knowing what she wants to do with her life.
她的确知道  她在1997年除夕做了什么
Well, she certainly knew what she was doing New Year's Eve, 1997.
我就知道你会那么说
I knew you were going to throw that in my face!
那是三年前的事  她一再地道歉
That was three years ago. She apologized and apologized.
你们还想怎么样
What more do you want?
我们要找回六年的时光
We want the last six years back!
我们也是
So do we! So do we!
很抱歉让你们看这一幕
I'm sorry you had to see that.
-早安  瑞秋  -嗨
- Morning, Rachel. - Hi.
昨晚你做了什么
Hey, so, what'd you do last night?
-我跟乔伊出去了 - 是吗
- Went out with Joey. - Yeah?
你们又去泡妞了
Another night of bird-dogging the chicas?
不  我们坐下来长谈
No, we had a really good talk.
我想我不会再去酒吧泡妞了
I don't think I'm gonna do that bar scene anymore.
我没想到你会那么说
Wow, I did not see that coming.
那不是真正的我
It's just not really who I am.
我一直都很快乐  我为什么要告诉你这件事
I've always been happier when... Why am I telling you this?
-你不会关心这种事不  -我很关心
- You don't care about this stuff. - Yes, I do.
你说到"我一直都很快乐"
You were saying, "I'm happier when I..."
当我谈恋爱时
When I'm in a relationship.
-我喜欢女朋友陪在身边  -真的吗
- I love having a girlfriend. - Really?
我可以好好宠溺她
Someone I can spoil, you know.
宠溺
Spoil?
我问你啊
Let me ask you something.
你相信我们都在寻找完美的另一半吗
Do you believe there's one perfect person for everyone?
我开始相信了
I'm starting to.
如果那人已经出现  你应该去争取对吧
If that persors in your life, should you do something about it?
对  当然
Yes. Hell, yes.
那就这么定了
All right, then, it's settled.
-我要跟我前女友复合  -我愿意
- I'm getting back together with my ex. - I would love to!
什么
What?
喂
Hello?
我应该会谈上一阵子  对不起
This is gonna be a while. Excuse me.
好
Yeah.
天啊
My God!
对不起  吵到你了吗
Oh, I'm sorry. Is that annoying?
说到在床上很自私  惠特妮还好吗
And speaking of being selfish in bed, how's Whitney?
也许她其实可以很无私
Maybe she wouldn't have to be selfish in bed...
如果另一个人知道正确位置的话
...if someone else knew where everything was.
他的确知道
Oh, he knows.
大部份啦
For the most part.
嘿  太好了  你们两个都在
Oh, hey. Good, you're both here.
我们得谈一谈
We kind of need to talk.
-两个人一起  -怎么了
- Both of you, together? - What's up?
昨晚我到凯尔家拿一些东西
Well, I went over to Kyle's last night to pick up a few things...
我们回忆了一些往事
...and we got to reminiscing.
几乎彻谈整晚
We talked most of the night...
我们明白  我们会这么气对方
...and realized the reason we're angry with each other...
是因为我们还对彼此有感觉
...is because there are still feelings there.
所以
So...
快说吧  凯尔
Oh, just say it, Kyle!
我们要重新开始
We're gonna try again.
你不是说她爱抱怨常常要人关注她吗
What about her whining, and her constant need for attention?
我会努力调整
I'm gonna work on that.
对  因为你很擅长改变
Right, because you're so capable of change.
他会边尿边哼歌
You know, he hums when he pees.
-我知道  -所以他都尿不准  随便啦
- I do know. - Makes him miss the bowl, but whatever.
我们很抱歉
We're so sorry.
没关系我们不需要你们  我已经忘了这件事
That's all right. We don't need you. I'm over it already.
对  我根本一点都不在乎
Yeah, and I don't even give a tiny rat's ass.
我们得走了
Yeah, we're gonna go.
对不起
I'm sorry.
菲比  你没有看错她
Pheebs, you were right about her.
她的确试图把性当成武器
You know, she did try to use sex as a weapon.
我的背真的好痛
Yeah, I hurt my back a little.
他做其他事时  也会哼歌
You know, he hums while he does other stuff too.
没有他们  我们能过得更好
We're better off without them.
如果他们再分手
Even if they break up again,
你最好别让他加入你的伤心男子俱乐部
you better not let him in your sad men's club.
-离婚男人俱乐部  -一样啦
- Divorced men's club. - Po-tay-to, po-tah-to.
大家快来看
Hey, guys, check it out.
-我妈把报纸寄给我  -我们来瞧瞧
- My mom sent me the paper. - Let's see it.
-看起来不错  -你们看起来很配
- Oh, yeah, that looks good. - You make a very attractive couple.
-对  我们是天生一对  -一点都没错
- Yeah, we look great together. - We really do.
好吧
Okay.
想像一下我们的孩子会是什么模样
Imagine what our kids would look like.
我们不必想像的
We don't have to imagine.
是我要娶她
I'm marrying her.
再看吧
We'll just see.